[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "JJR", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Could this now galvanize the Republican base vote to come out and cause you bigger problems than the success is worth enjoying in the short term?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "this", "now", "galvanize", "the", "Republican", "base", "vote", "to", "come", "out", "and", "cause", "you", "bigger", "problems", "than", "the", "success", "is", "worth", "enjoying", "in", "the", "short", "term", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Well, let me say first, Piers, something that may cause you and maybe some of your more cynical viewers to roll their eyes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "me", "say", "first", ",", "Piers", ",", "something", "that", "may", "cause", "you", "and", "maybe", "some", "of", "your", "more", "cynical", "viewers", "to", "roll", "their", "eyes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "What do you guys say to this charge now that really this is just what it is, it's just a new tax?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "guys", "say", "to", "this", "charge", "now", "that", "really", "this", "is", "just", "what", "it", "is", ",", "it", "'s", "just", "a", "new", "tax", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "Well, two things I would say.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "two", "things", "I", "would", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2005", "2006"]}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "But how do you explain to the public that the president didn't agree with it but now he's saluting it as a great triumph, given that you're trying to attack Mitt Romney for bringing a version of it in your state which apparently has done a lot of good?", "question_tokens": ["But", "how", "do", "you", "explain", "to", "the", "public", "that", "the", "president", "did", "n't", "agree", "with", "it", "but", "now", "he", "'s", "saluting", "it", "as", "a", "great", "triumph", ",", "given", "that", "you", "'re", "trying", "to", "attack", "Mitt", "Romney", "for", "bringing", "a", "version", "of", "it", "in", "your", "state", "which", "apparently", "has", "done", "a", "lot", "of", "good", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Well, the thing that the president didn't agree with is the same thing that I was skeptical of when I was running for governor back in 2005 and 2006.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "thing", "that", "the", "president", "did", "n't", "agree", "with", "is", "the", "same", "thing", "that", "I", "was", "skeptical", "of", "when", "I", "was", "running", "for", "governor", "back", "in", "2005", "and", "2006", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "RP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "So I guess you're foaming at the mouth with blind rage, are you?", "question_tokens": ["So", "I", "guess", "you", "'re", "foaming", "at", "the", "mouth", "with", "blind", "rage", ",", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Well, how about feeling very, very sad about what this means for our country but frankly very excited that the battle is joined and it will be a battle between now and November and the stakes are very clear.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "how", "about", "feeling", "very", ",", "very", "sad", "about", "what", "this", "means", "for", "our", "country", "but", "frankly", "very", "excited", "that", "the", "battle", "is", "joined", "and", "it", "will", "be", "a", "battle", "between", "now", "and", "November", "and", "the", "stakes", "are", "very", "clear", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 117, "question": "What is wrong with that in principle?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "wrong", "with", "that", "in", "principle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "How awkward is it for you that the guy that won the Republican race and now has to take on Barack Obama, what you sense is a vulnerable area, is the guy that basically inspired the whole plan to start with?", "question_tokens": ["How", "awkward", "is", "it", "for", "you", "that", "the", "guy", "that", "won", "the", "Republican", "race", "and", "now", "has", "to", "take", "on", "Barack", "Obama", ",", "what", "you", "sense", "is", "a", "vulnerable", "area", ",", "is", "the", "guy", "that", "basically", "inspired", "the", "whole", "plan", "to", "start", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Well, here's what I know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "here", "'s", "what", "I", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Massachusetts"]}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Shouldn't Mitt Romney just come out and say, you know what, this is basically what I brought in to Massachusetts, and it kind of worked, I salute you, Mr. President?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "n't", "Mitt", "Romney", "just", "come", "out", "and", "say", ",", "you", "know", "what", ",", "this", "is", "basically", "what", "I", "brought", "in", "to", "Massachusetts", ",", "and", "it", "kind", "of", "worked", ",", "I", "salute", "you", ",", "Mr.", "President", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Well, I think -- I think what you're seeing is it hasn't worked in Massachusetts.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "what", "you", "'re", "seeing", "is", "it", "has", "n't", "worked", "in", "Massachusetts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. President"], "LOCATION": ["Massachusetts"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "If it was such a catastrophic disaster in Massachusetts, Romneycare, why should we elect him as the president of the United States if he on this fundamental point got it all so horribly wrong?", "question_tokens": ["If", "it", "was", "such", "a", "catastrophic", "disaster", "in", "Massachusetts", ",", "Romneycare", ",", "why", "should", "we", "elect", "him", "as", "the", "president", "of", "the", "United", "States", "if", "he", "on", "this", "fundamental", "point", "got", "it", "all", "so", "horribly", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Well, I would just say this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "just", "say", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Massachusetts", "United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Do you think this is exactly the kind of issue that will galvanize and back into the action?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "this", "is", "exactly", "the", "kind", "of", "issue", "that", "will", "galvanize", "and", "back", "into", "the", "action", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "I don't -- I don't think there's any question.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "there", "'s", "any", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress", "Congress"]}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "Patrick, how do you think your father would have felt today?", "question_tokens": ["Patrick", ",", "how", "do", "you", "think", "your", "father", "would", "have", "felt", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "Well, I think he would have been thrilled that not just members of Congress have guaranteed health care anymore but that all the constituents that elected them now have access to health care that members of Congress are fully happy to have.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "he", "would", "have", "been", "thrilled", "that", "not", "just", "members", "of", "Congress", "have", "guaranteed", "health", "care", "anymore", "but", "that", "all", "the", "constituents", "that", "elected", "them", "now", "have", "access", "to", "health", "care", "that", "members", "of", "Congress", "are", "fully", "happy", "to", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "Were you shocked that Justice Roberts, Chief Justice Roberts, was the deciding vote today?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "shocked", "that", "Justice", "Roberts", ",", "Chief", "Justice", "Roberts", ",", "was", "the", "deciding", "vote", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "I was shocked that he was just the deciding vote.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "shocked", "that", "he", "was", "just", "the", "deciding", "vote", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Justice Roberts"], "PERSON": ["Justice Roberts"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "You must have been pretty shocked today, weren't you, by what happened?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "have", "been", "pretty", "shocked", "today", ",", "were", "n't", "you", ",", "by", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "I was -- I was surprised.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "--", "I", "was", "surprised", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "How do you think this is all going to play out now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "this", "is", "all", "going", "to", "play", "out", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Well, on the bottom line, people felt that the statute was in trouble because the oral argument seemed to go badly for the Obama administration.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "on", "the", "bottom", "line", ",", "people", "felt", "that", "the", "statute", "was", "in", "trouble", "because", "the", "oral", "argument", "seemed", "to", "go", "badly", "for", "the", "Obama", "administration", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "Jonathan Turley, as a professor of law on the panel tonight, from a legal perspective purely, do you think the Supreme Court acted correctly?", "question_tokens": ["Jonathan", "Turley", ",", "as", "a", "professor", "of", "law", "on", "the", "panel", "tonight", ",", "from", "a", "legal", "perspective", "purely", ",", "do", "you", "think", "the", "Supreme", "Court", "acted", "correctly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Well, I have mixed feelings about it quite frankly.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "mixed", "feelings", "about", "it", "quite", "frankly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Supreme Court"], "PERSON": ["Jonathan Turley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "I mean is it -- is what we've seen today, led by Chief Justice Roberts, is it a form of judicial activism do you think?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "is", "it", "--", "is", "what", "we", "'ve", "seen", "today", ",", "led", "by", "Chief", "Justice", "Roberts", ",", "is", "it", "a", "form", "of", "judicial", "activism", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", ",", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "It is a form of judicial activism.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "a", "form", "of", "judicial", "activism", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"], "PERSON": ["Justice Roberts"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "What is your opinion of who's the real winner and who's the lose today?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "opinion", "of", "who", "'s", "the", "real", "winner", "and", "who", "'s", "the", "lose", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Well, I think in situations like this, you probably don't want to get too cute and counterintuitive.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "in", "situations", "like", "this", ",", "you", "probably", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "get", "too", "cute", "and", "counterintuitive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Or is what happened today one of the reasons that so many people voted for Barack Obama in the first place?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "what", "happened", "today", "one", "of", "the", "reasons", "that", "so", "many", "people", "voted", "for", "Barack", "Obama", "in", "the", "first", "place", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "WP", "VBN", "NN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "What was rocking your boat there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "rocking", "your", "boat", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Well, Piers, you mentioned President Obama's promises when he ran for office in the first place.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "you", "mentioned", "President", "Obama", "'s", "promises", "when", "he", "ran", "for", "office", "in", "the", "first", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Ryan Lizza, what do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["Ryan", "Lizza", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "There's a lot of facts in there.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "facts", "in", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan Lizza"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "It's not a very credible position, is it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "a", "very", "credible", "position", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "I think Mitt Romney at this point has a chair in every corner of the room.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "Mitt", "Romney", "at", "this", "point", "has", "a", "chair", "in", "every", "corner", "of", "the", "room", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Are you sorry for what you did to her?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "sorry", "for", "what", "you", "did", "to", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "I am sorry.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "sorry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "If she were still alive, would you say to her, I'm sorry?", "question_tokens": ["If", "she", "were", "still", "alive", ",", "would", "you", "say", "to", "her", ",", "I", "'m", "sorry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "Pretty extraordinary, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Pretty", "extraordinary", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "Yeah, it was.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "it", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "They were both narcissists?", "question_tokens": ["They", "were", "both", "narcissists", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "I would say so very much.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "so", "very", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "Whose idea was it not to use birth control?", "question_tokens": ["Whose", "idea", "was", "it", "not", "to", "use", "birth", "control", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "We are both adults.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "are", "both", "adults", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "We were in love.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "were", "in", "love", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "What were you both thinking?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "you", "both", "thinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "We weren't.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "were", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "agree", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "Absolutely agree.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "agree", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120628pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "How do you think your public perception is right now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "your", "public", "perception", "is", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "Destroyer, villain, evil, basher, all of that.", "answer_tokens": ["Destroyer", ",", "villain", ",", "evil", ",", "basher", ",", "all", "of", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]